BUDOGAOKA BANK
GREAT YEAR-END LOTTERY
MORIOH STATION BRANCH
PROMISSORY NOTE
BUDOGAOKA BANK
MORIOH STATION BRANCH
TOTAL 5,000,000 YEN
PLEASE PAY THE AMOUNT STATED
ABOVE IN EXCHANGE FOR
THIS PROMISSORY NOTE.
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 19
SHIGECHI'S HARVEST, PART 2
RECEPTION
ICHIRO MORISHITA
MORI
MORISHITA ICHIRO
KINOSHITA ICHIRO
CRUSH
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
LIQUOR
SMASH
WHACK
BAM
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
- CURRENT SAVINGS - 1,666,666 YEN
EPISODE 20
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
DREAMS OF CINDERELLA